Had not intended to become an officer, had not intended to be a pilot.
Now I'm all three.
There is a picture that pilots are some kind of über people.
We are not.
It's about being specific more than special.
One cliché that people say is "One day is not the same."
Here, weekdays are incredibly similar.
We follow the same routine.
It is weather brief, air traffic conductor review
Air pass and debrief.
What is good is the great contrasts between the weeks.
So there is a lot to read too.
The flight itself is quite unpublished
But we have to keep a good shape.
So training is a big part too.
Late obviously a sense of freedom
to get to rush forward
between cobbles and cuts
The sun sparkles and
You see the waves go a little.
It is also wonderful of course.
My name is Freddy and I am a helicopter pilot.